EN / [JP](https://www.loopsessions.com/jp/privacy/)

* [Top  
    Home](https://www.loopsessions.com/)
* [Works  
    Development](https://www.loopsessions.com/work/)
* [Company  
    Information](https://www.loopsessions.com/company/)
* [Press  
    Published](https://www.loopsessions.com/press/)
* [Support  
    Contact us](https://www.loopsessions.com/support/)
* [Blog  
    Our blog](https://www.loopsessions.com/blog/)

### Privacy policy

Loop-Sessions.LLC. positions the protection of customer's personal information as an important item, and will establish and implement the following privacy policy.  

About acquisition of personal information and purpose of use
------------------------------------------------------------

When we acquire your personal information through this website, we will acquire it by an appropriate method, clarify the purpose of use, and handle it after obtaining your consent. In addition, the acquired personal information will be handled within the scope necessary for the purpose of use.  

About disclosure of personal information to third parties
---------------------------------------------------------

We will not disclose personal information to a third party without the prior consent of the individual, except when permitted by law.  

About access log
----------------

This site records the information of the person who accessed the site as an access log. The access log includes the access date and time, IP address, etc. We do not use it for the purpose of collecting personal information.  

Copyright(C) Loop-Sessions.LLC. All rights reserved.
